ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
Goodness, I'm exhausted.
Do you know?
Xiao Run is really something.
He posted 500 portraits of you
in the city.
Five hundred…
Portraits.
Shangque,
the servant Qu Shui, and I
spent four hours taking them down.
My legs are slimmer now.
It was all because of your bad idea.
You not only kept Xiao Run
and Xie Wanqing from meeting,
but also encouraged Xiao Run
with his fairy in the painting.
If Xie Wanying fails her tribulation,
thus ruining my plan,
I will send you to Silver Lake
to dig rocks and mine.
Don't blame Jieli for that.
It's because you are too charming.
You met Lady Wanqing under the moonlight
and made her fall in love with you
at first sight.
The fairy in the painting
is exaggerating my charms.
Why is her dream lover being so modest?
Good things take time.
Don't worry too much.
Persuade the lord.
Now you want to order me around?
You ordered Qu Shui around
and smiled at him today.
Didn't you have a lot of fun?
Why are you acting weirdly too?
I just don't understand
why you are so interested
in Qu Shui.
That's because his stupidity is amusing.
He's a fool just like his master.
You always say that I am
the stupidest person in the three realms.
Can he be stupider than me?
Stupid Black Dragon,
if you want to be the best at something,
shouldn't it be something good?
That's not what I mean.
Then what do you mean?
- Stop arguing.
Forget it.
Let's be serious.
Jieli, it has been a long day.
They still haven't even met each other.
What should we do?
I…
Are you still counting on her?
Forget it.
In my opinion, I had better go to Xiao Run
and talk to him face-to-face
to make him give up.
Talk to him face-to-face?
He is obsessed with you right now.
If you meet him now,
I'm afraid you will be married tomorrow.
This won't do and that won't do.
Then tell me. What should we do?
I got it.
Orchid, if you want to meet Xiao Run,
you can.
But not like this.
All right.
Perfect.
If Xiao Run sees his desired fairy
looking like this,
I'm sure he will lose interest.
Here, take a look.
Isn't it too…
No, she isn't ugly enough.
I'll do it myself.
Moon Supreme Lord, no need.
No.
Since it is to make Xiao Run give up,
the uglier, the better.
Changheng has become a mortal now
and still likes
an ordinary girl like you.
My lord is really good at applying makeup.
If Xiao Run takes a look at Orchid now,
he will surely have nightmares.
Do you remember what I said?
Be as rude as I can be.
Be as vulgar as I can be.
After meeting Xiao Run today,
I must make sure
his love for me will be gone.
What is the hurry?
You used to be lazy
and refused to get up early.
Now you're so eager to see Xiao Run.
I'm just hoping
he can complete his tribulation soon.
Moon Supreme Lord,
look at how much I'm sacrificing.
Do you still not believe
that I have no feelings for Xiao Run?
There is no rush.
Go after noon passes.
Let Xiao Run wait for a long time.
His impression of you will be even worse.
Fine, I'll listen to you.
DONGFANG MANSION
Remember.
Keep your distance from him when you talk.
Don't look at him.
Don't smile at him.
Don't go to secluded places.
Moon Supreme Lord,
why are you so weird today?
Why are you so talkative and overcautious?
Are you so worried about me?
You talk too much.
- I'm leaving.
- Wait.
What is this?
Food.
I'm leaving.
Xiao Run.
The fairy in the painting?
It really is you.
You really came.
"Fairy in the painting"?
That's so mysterious.
What a stupid name.
I don't like it.
Also,
why are you staring at me?
She is acting so oddly.
Maybe she is
testing me.
Miss, you misunderstood me.
I just thought
I had never seen
a woman wear such an original look.
This makeup is deliberately bold.
And this flower crown
is refreshing and elegant.
I think only you,
someone unworldly and elegant,
can pull it off.
I'm so late. Aren't you angry?
Why would I be angry?
You put such thought into your appearance.
You must have greatly valued this meeting.
Naturally, I should wait for you longer.
I would wait several days,
let alone half a day.
Is something wrong with Xiao Run's eyes?
Beauty is in the eye of the beholder.
No, I'll have to go.
My lord, they just met.
Why don't we wait a little longer?
I thought
that it was just a meeting in a dream.
I didn't think
that I would really see you today.
How dare you say that?
I…
I'm here to question you.
Why do you have a painting of me?
You even posted it all over Lucheng.
It's so ugly.
It didn't even show a bit of my beauty.
You are right.
You are so extraordinary.
But I'm not good at painting.
I couldn't draw a bit of your beauty.
But don't worry.
I will practice more in the future.
When I get home,
I'll make another painting
based on your look today.
No!
There is no need to.
Lord Changheng has become a mortal.
His personality has changed a lot,
but he is still so gentle.
I'm being unreasonable,
but he isn't angry at all.
I will have to continue to annoy him.
I've been tired all day.
I'm exhausted.
I can't walk anymore.
Let me massage my feet.
It's so comfortable.
He is sure to dislike me now.
I used to think that I was uninhibited.
But you are the one who truly is.
Wonderful.
How satisfying.
No, I must go there.
My lord.
Xiao Run must not be killed.
Please think twice, my lord.
Who said I wanted to kill him?
She is fearful.
She can't even act.
We can't count on her.
Making Xiao Run lose interest
will have to be up to me.
My lord.
You are indeed extraordinary
like a fairy out of this world.
To be honest…
This may offend you,
but I have to say it.
I keep getting the feeling
that you and I are destined
to be together.
There you are, honey.
I've been looking for you.
Mr. Dongfang?
Big Blockhead.
Why did you come too?
What are you doing?
The floor is cold. Be careful, honey.
Don't move.
Mr. Dongfang, how could you do this?
My wife has been married to me
for three years.
Who is married to you?
Honey, why are you still angry with me?
I…
You're pregnant.
It is hard on you.
I shouldn't have made you angry.
I know I was wrong.
You're pregnant.
You shouldn't eat too many bowls of ice.
I was too anxious,
so I said those harsh words.
After our child is born,
I'll take you all over Lucheng
and let you eat whatever you want.
You've gone too far.
Being married is ridiculous enough.
But you even claim that I'm pregnant.
Not even Jieli could come up
with such a terrible lie.
How can you make Xiao Run give up
without something so outrageous?
This is too much.
Look at him.
Do you already feel sorry for him?
I don't.
Let's go, honey.
Let's go home.
That's right.
Xiao Run.
We are friends.
I didn't want to bring up the past.
I thought that if you couldn't find her,
you would give up after a few days.
To my surprise,
my wife got angry with me today,
so she agreed to your invitation
and caused this misunderstanding.
I…
I won't blame the ignorant.
Give the painting of my wife back.
Honey, let's go.
We've gone so far.
Why don't you let me go?
Honey, you are wrong.
If Xiao Run comes after us,
our lie will be exposed.
Who is your wife?
Why are you addicted to acting?
Why are you still mad at me, honey?
Let go of me.
What is that?
Haven't you seen it before?
Come with me.
Wait.
Am I going like this?
Can you help me become beautiful again?
Have you decided yet?
No?
My wish is to destroy Shuiyuntian,
kill all those hypocritical immortals,
and tell my father the good news.
Then I'll unify the three realms
so that the people of Cangyan Sea
will suffer less
from disease, disaster, and harm,
and never suffer the pain of separation.
But I will do these
by myself.
Why do I need to pray
to heaven with a sky lantern?
That should be the case.
Why would I expect anything else from him?
What about you?
Why haven't you written it yet?
I haven't decided yet.
I'm the Supreme Lord of the three realms.
Rather than relying on a sky lantern,
you might as well beg me.
If I am happy, I might fulfill your wish.
Really?
I always keep my word.
My wish is actually very simple.
My wish is simply
for the Wangchuan River to be free of war
and for splendid days without weapons.
You're trying again
to persuade me not to wage war.
For tens of thousands of years,
the Moon Tribe has suffered
the pain of separation and rebellion.
Once the war starts,
be it the Moon Tribe or the Fairy Tribe,
how many tragedies will be repeated?
You don't want Shuiyuntian
to be ravaged by war.
Then what about the pain of betrayal
that my ancestors suffered
and the humiliation
that the people of Cangyan Sea endured?
Cangyan Sea's 100,000 soldiers
have been sealed
in the Xuanxu Realm for 30,000 years.
They are also someone's sons,
husbands, and fathers.
They also want to go home.
I grew up in Shuiyuntian.
And he is the Moon Supreme of Cangyan Sea.
People of the Moon Tribe
and the Fairy Tribe cannot…
I'm sorry, we were having a good time.
Let's not talk about that.
Let's write our wishes.
All right.
Orchid,
I want you to stay by my side forever.
Big Blockhead,
although I can't stay with you forever,
I hope you will always be safe and happy,
surrounded by friends, brothers,
loyalty, and love,
and never lonely again.
THE BRIGHT MOON SHINES OVER THE SEA
FROM AFAR
WE SHARE THIS MOMENT TOGETHER
Wanqing, think about it some more.
I've made up my mind.
You don't have to persuade me.
Lady Wanqing.
Lady Orchid, you're here.
What's going on?
Lady Orchid,
as you said,
the Dark Golden Glory blossomed
just when I made up my mind.
This is a good omen.
These are the assets
that I have accumulated over ten years
at Flying Immortal Pavilion.
Look at this luminous pearl.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes,
it is.
I've used the assets that I saved
to buy my freedom.
From now on, I am free.
I can go in search of my dream lover.
What?
Is that why…
Yes.
But…
But you don't know
whether he likes you or not.
That's right.
If you don't leave yourself a way out,
then even if he takes you,
when your beauty fades
and he loses interest in you later,
you won't have any money
to support yourself.
- Wanqing.
- That's right.
I can't forget the sight of him.
That is enough for me.
Life is short.
Since I'm certain that this fated person
is not a dream,
then no matter what,
I don't want to leave any regrets.
From now on,
I won't have any valuable flowers
for you to look after.
Don't say that.
We are friends.
Hearing you say that
makes me glad to have met you.
But…
Has he not given up yet?
Mr. Dongfang.
After I got home yesterday
and thought about the huge mistake
I almost made,
I couldn't sleep at night.
I'm here to ask for your forgiveness.
This is water under the bridge.
Don't mention it again.
I can't.
The face and figure
of the fairy in the painting
continue to linger in my mind.
I'm afraid
I'll never meet another
who will stir my heart so.
But don't get me wrong.
I may be a playboy,
but I will never steal another man's love.
I promise, from now on,
I will never appear
in front of your wife again.
I've decided
to leave this sad place
to garrison the border in the north.
What?
Once I leave,
I'm afraid I won't be able
to play cuju, play chess, drink, and chat
with you for several years.
For several years?
If Xiao Run leaves Lucheng,
how can he and Xie Wanqing
get married during the Flower Festival?
Xiao Run, it's getting late.
We have to get on the road.
Mr. Dongfang.
Take care.
Wait.
These two are mortals now,
but they're still so troublesome.
We have to part eventually.
Let us bid farewell here.
Xiao…
Xiao Run,
are you really leaving?
I somehow think
that I should give this stone
to my destined one.
But fate plays cruel tricks.
Mr. Dongfang and Lady Orchid
are the perfect match.
But I'm very grateful
that you came to see me off today.
I heard that the northern prairie is vast.
Maybe seeing the beautiful view
might lessen my sorrow.
Do something.
It's all your fault.
Well…
Then…
There is nothing to see
in the cold and harsh frontier.
Xiao Run, it was just a misunderstanding.
I don't blame you anymore.
Don't be impulsive.
Yes.
I know you don't want me to leave.
But I've made up my mind.
Xiao Run, why don't you reconsider?
Xiao Run, if we delay any longer,
we won't reach
the courier station by nightfall.
I see.
I have only known you for a short time.
But for 18 years,
these few days have been
the happiest time of my life.
In the future,
if you experience snow in Lucheng
or wind from the north,
it must be because I am missing you all.
Goodbye.
Jieli.
Hurry.
What should we do? Go.
I'm thinking.
- Jieli.
- I'm thinking.
I'm thinking.
- Hurry.
- I'm thinking.
He's leaving, Jieli.
Have you figured it out, Jieli?
Xiao Run!
Congratulations.
You passed the test.
Test?
Let me introduce her to you again.
Lady Orchid
is the biological sister of Mr. Dongfang.
As her elder brother,
Mr. Dongfang treats Lady Orchid
like a treasure.
Xiao Run,
you claimed that you love Lady Orchid,
but you acted so absurdly.
You even posted paintings
all over Lucheng.
For such a strange thing,
of course my lord
couldn't let his sister marry you.
So we came up with a plan
for them to act like a couple
to see how you would handle it.
But today,
you came up with such a perfect solution.
It not only
measures up to your love for Lady Orchid,
but it also preserves your friendship
with Mr. Dongfang.
It is clear to see
that your personality and character
are impeccable.
Mr. Dongfang, isn't that right?
Yes.
Are you really siblings?
What is the test?
Fool.
It means
that you are allowed to marry Lady Orchid.
My brother-in-law, please accept my bow.
You…
Aren't you going to garrison the north?
I'm not going anywhere.
Don't get cocky too soon.
You keep saying you like Orchid.
You like my sister.
Do you know what love is?
How will you prove it?
I feel very close with Lady Orchid.
I seem to have seen her somewhere.
That doesn't count.
Aren't parents and siblings close too?
That's right.
The moment I saw Qu Shui,
I felt close to him too.
I feel like I've seen him somewhere.
I will treat Lady Orchid very well,
cherish her, and protect her.
I won't let anyone bully her.
I can handle that on my own.
Yes.
Mr. Dongfang and Lady Orchid are close.
Of course I'm no match.
Are these insincere speeches all you know?
To be honest,
I have lived carefree
over the years.
I always felt that I was
the happiest person in the world.
Being spanked and lectured
were inconsequential to me.
That was until I…
That was until I dreamed of Lady Orchid.
I couldn't find her.
I kept searching
and couldn't stop thinking about her.
That day when Mr. Dongfang tested me
and I thought that I had
no chance with Lady Orchid in this life,
I felt empty inside.
Lady Orchid, your makeup today
is refreshing and elegant.
The day we met,
it must have been a test.
But everything I said that day
was sincere.
Whatever you want in the future--
Enough.
My lord.
It's inappropriate to talk about this now.
I'll go home,
inform my father,
and prepare betrothal gifts.
Leave now.
Yes.
Let's go.
Look at what you've done.
Do something about it.
- What do we do?
- My lord.
I don't know.
I have the same feeling.
Is this love?
My lord, all 3,000 guards are here.
No one escaped.
Don't look so sad.
My lord, here. Have some grapes.
Eat it yourself.
You won't get any
when you are towing boats at Silver Lake.
What are you talking about?
Why would I be doing that?
The current situation is great.
Great?
Even I can see it.
It's all ruined.
Jieli.
What should we do now?
Xiao Run is busy
preparing betrothal gifts to marry me.
Lady Wanqing is determined
to buy her freedom
and marry Moon Supreme Lord.
What should we do?
Everything now
is still going according to the fate poem.
She meets her beloved
during the Lantern Festival
and buys her freedom to get married.
Next is the wedding ceremony
during the Flower Festival.
She dies at the sword
of the groom, Xiao Run.
But she wants to marry me,
not Xiao Run.
Yes, the groom is not Xiao Run.
I know.
Calm down.
Everyone is being too narrow-minded.
Here's what I mean.
What if there are two weddings
during the Flower Festival?
Do you mean…
Seven words.
Steal the beam to replace the pillar.
Orchid, agree to marry Xiao Run.
The lord will agree to marry Xie Wanqing.
We will prepare the weddings together.
On the wedding night
during the Flower Festival,
we will make a swap.
Jieli.
I've known you for over 1,000 years.
I knew you were immoral,
but I didn't know it was to this extent.
You flatter me.
Will this work?
The bride and groom are all fake.
Why not?
We just need to follow the fate poem.
On the wedding night,
as long as Xiao Run kills Xie Wanqing,
then they will pass their tribulations.
The details aren't important.
I won't allow it.
Marriage is not child's play.
My lord objects.
So I object too.
Do you have any of your own opinions?
My lord,
there is no alternative though.
I agree.
Although the process is different,
as long as the result
matches the fate poem,
the tribulation will be completed.
It can work.
Didn't you just say it was immoral?
I…
Isn't the most important thing now
to ensure Lord Changheng and Lady Chidi
successfully pass their tribulations
and keep their primordial spirits safe?
As long as we can achieve this goal,
we can take unconventional measures.
The Flower Festival is coming up.
Moon Supreme Lord, tomorrow…
No, today,
take betrothal gifts
to propose to Lady Wanqing.
Don't forget that it's all fake.
Fake.
I don't care if it's fake or not.
I only marry the woman I like.
As for others,
I will not even look at them,
not to mention proposing a marriage.